<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lost Leaf Studio</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/</link><description>Recent content on Lost Leaf Studio</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lostleafstudio.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cribbage Scoring Pegboard</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/cribbage-scoring-pegboard/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/cribbage-scoring-pegboard/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Leave your pegboard at home and use this application to keep track of your cribbage score. Allows for easily adding each players score and displaying the score on a virtual pegboard. Works for two player games only and has multiple themes to choose from including a dark theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Cribbage Scoring Pegboard app also includes cribbage rules of the game and a handy cribbage scoring chart for easy reference. Making this a great companion app for playing cribbage. So grab a deck of cards, this app, and have some fun!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/privacy/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="privacy-policy"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;June 22, 2020&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your privacy is important to us. It is Lost Leaf Studio&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you through our app, Cribbage Scoring Pegboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/privacy_policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/privacy_policy/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="privacy-policy"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;June 22, 2020&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lost Leaf Studio built the Retro Raid app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Lost Leaf Studio and is intended for use as is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>River Raid Classic</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/river-raid-classic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/river-raid-classic/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Enjoy this tribute to an Atari 2600 classic River Raid. Relive your childhood adventures on the river of no return. Available now for iOS and Android.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your mission is to score as many points possible by destroying enemy tankers, helicopters, fuel depots, jets and bridges before your jet crashes or runs out of fuel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn to fly successful missions, you&amp;rsquo;ll need the sensitivity, touch and sharpshooting skills of a precision jet pilot. But that takes time and practice.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy - Cribbage Scoring Pegboard</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/privacy-policy/cribbage-scoring-pegboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/privacy-policy/cribbage-scoring-pegboard/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="privacy-policy---cribbage-scoring-pegboard"&gt;Privacy Policy - Cribbage Scoring Pegboard&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Effective Date: &lt;em&gt;January 1, 2026&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lost Leaf Studio, LLC (“we,” “us,” or “our”) respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how the mobile game Cribbage Scoring Pegboard handles user information. Cribbage Scoring Pegboard is an offline arcade-style game and is designed to operate without collecting or transmitting personal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="information-we-collect"&gt;Information We Collect&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not collect, store, process, or transmit any personal or non-personal data.
This includes, but is not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy - River Raiders</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/privacy-policy/river-raiders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/privacy-policy/river-raiders/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="privacy-policy---river-raiders"&gt;Privacy Policy - River Raiders&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Effective Date: &lt;em&gt;January 1, 2026&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lost Leaf Studio, LLC (“we,” “us,” or “our”) respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how the mobile game River Raiders handles user information. River Raiders is an offline arcade-style game and is designed to operate without collecting or transmitting personal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="information-we-collect"&gt;Information We Collect&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not collect, store, process, or transmit any personal or non-personal data.
This includes, but is not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>