<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>App on Lost Leaf Studio</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/tags/app/</link><description>Recent content in App on Lost Leaf Studio</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://lostleafstudio.com/tags/app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cribbage Scoring Pegboard</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/cribbage-pegboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/cribbage-pegboard/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Leave your pegboard at home and use this application to keep track of your cribbage score. Allows for easily adding each players score and displaying the score on a virtual pegboard. Works for two player games only and has multiple themes to choose from including a dark theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Cribbage Scoring Pegboard app also includes cribbage rules of the game and a handy cribbage scoring chart for easy reference. Making this a great companion app for playing cribbage. So grab a deck of cards, this app, and have some fun!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>River Raiders</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/river-raid-classic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/river-raid-classic/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Enjoy this tribute to an Atari 2600 classic River Raid. Relive your childhood adventures on the river of no return. Available now for iOS and Android.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your mission is to score as many points possible by destroying enemy tankers, helicopters, fuel depots, jets and bridges before your jet crashes or runs out of fuel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn to fly successful missions, you&amp;rsquo;ll need the sensitivity, touch and sharpshooting skills of a precision jet pilot. But that takes time and practice.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>River Raiders</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/river-raiders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/river-raiders/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Take to the skies in River Raiders, a modern tribute to one of the most iconic top-down shooters of the classic console era. Navigate the River of No Return, strike enemy forces, manage your fuel, and push your skills to survive farther than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your mission is simple: fly fast, shoot straight, and stay alive. Enemy tankers, helicopters, jets, fuel depots, and fortified bridges crowd every stretch of the river. Precision flying and sharp reaction time are the difference between a clean run and a fiery crash.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>