<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>App on Lost Leaf Studio</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/tags/app/</link><description>Recent content in App on Lost Leaf Studio</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://lostleafstudio.com/tags/app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cribbage Pegboard</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/cribbage-pegboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/cribbage-pegboard/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Turn your phone into a digital cribbage pegboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cribbage Pegboard&lt;/strong&gt; lets you keep score while playing cribbage with real cards. It replaces a physical cribbage board with a clear, easy-to-read virtual pegboard, making it ideal for home games, travel, or casual play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built specifically for two-player cribbage, the app makes adding points fast and intuitive while keeping the classic pegboard feel players expect. No distractions, no ads, and no in-app purchases.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>River Raiders</title><link>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/river-raiders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lostleafstudio.com/apps/river-raiders/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Take to the skies in &lt;strong&gt;River Raiders&lt;/strong&gt;, a modern tribute to one of the most iconic top-down shooters of the classic console era. Navigate the River of No Return, strike enemy forces, manage your fuel, and push your skills to survive farther than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your mission is simple: fly fast, shoot straight, and stay alive. Enemy tankers, helicopters, jets, fuel depots, and fortified bridges crowd every stretch of the river. Precision flying and sharp reaction time are the difference between a clean run and a fiery crash.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>